{
    "subject": "resource/Katherine_Vaz",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_people_of_Portuguese_descent",
    "human_readable": "Katherine Vaz's subject category is American people of Portuguese descent.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9695063233375549,
            "question": "What defines Katherine Vaz as an American person of Portuguese descent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.938780665397644,
            "question": "Are there any notable American people of Portuguese descent besides Katherine Vaz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8426753282546997,
            "question": "What is Katherine Vaz's subject category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6128748655319214,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of the cultural contributions of American people of Portuguese descent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6106640696525574,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics or experiences shared by Americans of Portuguese descent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6038320064544678,
            "question": "To which nationality does Katherine Vaz belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.581387996673584,
            "question": "From what country are Katherine Vaz's ancestors originally from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4292963147163391,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Katherine Vaz's heritage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2803618907928467,
            "question": "Is Katherine Vaz known for anything related to her dual heritage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27688848972320557,
            "question": "How does Katherine Vaz's heritage influence her life and work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Katherine Vaz's subject category is American people of Portuguese descent.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1694_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Katherine Vaz known for anything related to her dual heritage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1694_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Katherine Vaz's heritage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1694_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From what country are Katherine Vaz's ancestors originally from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1694_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1694_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain information about Katherine Vaz being the first Portuguese-American to have her work recorded by the Library of Congress, and also mention her Portuguese heritage. This suggests that she is indeed an American person of Portuguese descent."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Katherine Vaz\u2019s subject matter includes stories about American people of Portuguese descent. Specifically, several references are made to her novels and works focusing on Madeira (an island in Portugal), Portuguese heritage, and experiences of Portuguese immigrants in the United States during historical periods such as the Civil War era."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}